The crime saga of the digital age.
Deep Web is a documentary film directed by Alex Winter.
Deep Web gives the inside story of one of the most important and riveting digital crime sagas of the century -- the arrest of Ross William
Ulbricht, the 30-year-old entrepreneur convicted of being 'Dread Pirate Roberts,' creator and operator of online black market Silk Road.
As the only film with exclusive access to the Ulbricht family, Deep Web explores how the brightest minds and thought leaders behind the Deep Web and Bitcoin are now
caught in the crosshairs of the battle for control of a future inextricably linked to technology, with our digital rights hanging in the balance.
Narrator, played by Keanu Reeves.
Self, played by Ross Ulbricht.
Self, played by Cody Wilson.
Self, played by Lyn Ulbricht.
Self, played by Kirk Ulbricht.
Self, played by Andy Greenberg.
Deep Web: The Untold Story of Bitcoin and the Silk Road is a 2015 documentary-film directed by Alex
Winter, chronicling events surrounding Silk Road, bitcoin and the politics of the dark web.
Covering the trial of Ross Ulbricht, the documentary features interviews
with Wired writer Andy Greenberg and developer Amir Taaki.
Deep Web features narration from actor Keanu Reeves.
The film premiered at the 2015 South By Southwest film festival,
and aired on the Epix network on May 31, 2015.
The film explores themes of politics, war on drugs,
internet, drugs, criminal trial.
The tone is thought_provoking.